When we’re together we’re stronger
肩并肩 我们会更强大
Let’s go all up high let’s go discover
让我们全力以赴奔跑寻找
Cause we know we are going to make it
因为我们知道能够达到
Just believe we can do this really
只要坚信就好
We’re not alone or even owned
我们自由不孤单
So now we must seize this moment
不要放过这次机会
Never hide or never lose
不要躲藏不要迷茫
Every time we’re right on target
无论何时目标就在前方
So let’s just keep going
不要停下脚步
Cause we’re gonna keep on winning
因为我们不会失败
Sharing dreams you and me
倾诉你我的远方
All the hopes that we’ve been waiting
还有等待着的梦想
If you reach out I’ll be there for you
伸出手 我就在这里
There’s nothing I would not do for you
我会为你倾尽一切
When troubles are coming
当困难来临
We’ll fight them all together not alone
我们一起面对 绝不食言
All we do is just WIN
我们所做的都是为了胜利
Cause we know that we’ll WIN
因为我们知道我们将会胜利
We lift us up high we help each other to win it
肩并肩 我们一路进发直至胜利
All we do is just WIN
我们所做的都是为了胜利
我们所做的都是为了胜利.
Cause we know that we’ll WIN
因为我们知道我们将会胜利